残酷な天使のように 少年よ 神話になれ
青い風が今 胸のドアを叩いても 私だけをただ見つめて 微笑んでるあなた
そっと触れるもの 求めることに夢中で
運命さえまだ知らない 痛い気な瞳
だけどいつか気づくでしょう その背中には
遥か未来 目指すための羽があること
残酷な天使の転生 窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
ほとばしる 熱いパトスで 思い出を裏切るなら
この空を抱いて輝く 少年よ 神話になれ
お手 imag94关でお問い合わる 神話に絞りかけない
緊張 чер辺の神話に 図面は明確な through 물론
明日があなたたちの人が具体に回復するもの
反復に対翼のような Fatal Stark 深度 身体っ悪させません
Yes. Killing herself and leaving such a young girl behind is so awful.
Perhaps. But I believe there may have been some additional causes.
Oscar, darling. Mama cooked your favorite for you.
Oh, no. You mustn't complain about what you like and dislike.
Or that girl over there will laugh at you.
She just sits there every day, talking to that doll as if it were her real daughter.
I think it's because of the guilt she must feel.
She devoted her entire life to her research, not to taking care of her own daughter.
I fear your grief.
It's like looking at porcelain figures of a mother and her child.
Perhaps there really isn't much difference between humans and dolls.
Mankind creates dolls in our own image.
If God exists, perhaps we're all just a bunch of dolls to him.
Hmm. Hearing you say something like that makes it hard for me to believe that you're a modern physician.
I may be a doctor, but I'm a human being and a woman first.
You're a strong girl, Oscar.
But it's all right if you have to cry.
I'll never cry, Grandmother. I have to take care of myself now.
Oscar, your sink ratio has dropped an entire eight points. Don't think about anything else. Just concentrate the way you used to.
I'm trying to!
Oscar's sink ratio is getting lower and lower. What does it mean, ma'am?
It means trouble. We don't have a spare.
Let's concentrate our efforts on fixing Unit Zero.
We can't waste time on the one we might not be able to use.
Hmm.
The mitosis process in the left arm of Unit 2 has cleared the numerical requirement. Code 3.
Development of necrosis is currently under 0.05.
The current status of Unit Zero's regeneration is stable. Connecting receptors to the secondary terminal.
The Ava series was created from the Angel known as Adam.
Now, in order to defeat the Angels, we are employing the same forces which caused a second impact and wiped out half the human race.
Only humans could be so foolish as to attempt to harness the engine of our own destruction.
I hate the Avas. Is our revenge worth this?
Major Katsuraki!
They've started construction on all the Avas through Unit 13? At seven different locations around the world?
Yeah, this information came via Shanghai. My source is reliable.
Why are they speeding up the construction process now?
Well, we've lost two Avas recently, and two more Avas are severely damaged.
So I'd assume they're accelerating for the purpose of creating a reserve force.
Perhaps. But we've been receiving spare parts from Germany that were originally intended for Avas Units 5 and 6.
They've been spending an awful lot of cash lately.
And that's after they just doubled the existing budget.
I think the executives are being driven by something.
Yeah, I can almost feel the committee's impatience behind this.
Do you think they're doing this in anticipation of having to intercept multiple Angels at once,
rather than the singular probes we've seen thus far?
Hmm. Except that there's no reason for them to be doing that outside of official channels.
There's got to be some of the reason for this.
This is the first time all three of us have gotten together in a while. Why is there such an air of glue?
Hmm. I'm finished now.
Asuka! Why should I get it? It's probably just Kaji calling for you. You should answer your own phone.
He won't call again.
Ah! The invincible Shinji stoops to answering the phone! He doesn't just save the world!
Yes. Hello?
Damn him! I hate the way he ignores me!
Huh?
It's a call from Germany, Asuka. I think it's your mother.
A call from me? My mother?
Give me that!
Hello?
Hello, Muti!
Aha!
When she speaks in a language I can't understand, Asuka seems to be a different person.
You're very popular!
Haha!
Ach!
Ah!
Niemals!
Er ist ein selber Mensch!
Ja?
Wörtlich?
Ah, so.
Das ist aber toll!
Ich werde jetzt in Bett gehen.
Auf Wiederhören!
Gute Nacht!
Wow, you two were on the phone quite a while.
Well, it was just a routine communication.
I wish I talked to my family.
It's overrated.
And it's just for show.
She's not my real mother anyway.
Huh?
It's not like I hate her or anything.
I just feel like...
Why the hell am I telling all of this to you?!
I'm sorry.
I've really hit rock bottom when I get sympathy from a loser like you!
You!
Synchrograph minus 12.8.
It's barely over the starting indicator.
That's pathetic.
That's a worse score than yesterday.
Asuka's not feeling well today.
It's her period.
Sync ratios aren't influenced by physical changes.
The problem's deeper, in her subconscious.
It looks like we may have to replace Unit 2's pilot.
Asuka!
You're finished now.
You know, Asuka's pride has been badly damaged.
It's hard to blame her after she was defeated so badly.
But what's worse is that she feels like she was beaten by Shinji.
Maybe it's time the three of us stopped living together.
So you've hit your limit?
Your nice synthetic family is falling apart?
I don't have to take that from someone who tries to fill the holes in her own empty life with a bunch of cats.
I'm sorry. I'm just upset.
Why do I have to suffer through this just because I'm a girl?
It's not like I want to have children anyway.
The Route 7 loop is currently closed due to an accident.
Please use Route 12 at the gate board.
132.
153.
Definitely.
The Insthower 7 loop is 6 to 161.
So here's our Dean ofmos in theurka.
Aperformance.
1611.
Para the Обacumen.
2589.
1711.
1934.
If you don't open your mind to her, your Ava will not move.
You're saying this is my fault?
I'm blocking myself?
Yes.
Ava has its own mind.
It's just a big toy.
Then you don't know.
Ha!
Now I know something's up when Wonder Girl starts talking to me.
What's up?
Aren't you happy that I'm having trouble with my Ava now?
Well, don't worry, because when the next angel comes, our invincible Shinji will riot and destroy it.
We little girls won't have to fight anymore.
They only need that pathetic Shinji.
I thought it was bad when Shinji was nice, but when an emotionless wind-up doll like you starts being sympathetic, I'm doomed.
I am not a doll.
You are!
You do anything you're ordered to, don't you?
You'd kill yourself if your commander told you to, wouldn't you?
Of course.
Then you are a robot, just like I thought.
You're an unthinking, emotionless pup, and I hate you.
I hate you!
I hate everyone!
Oh my God!
Man, it looks like Shinji didn't show up again today.
Rey misses class all the time, but...
Asuka's gone too, and Suzuhara's still in the hospital.
The situation must be really bad.
They're all gone.
AVA Unit 2 signals auto-marrow.
Connection of the A's is within normal limits.
The field of proliferation is within the expected range.
You're my doll, and you're supposed to do whatever I tell you to without arguing.
Do you understand?
Why does a weapon need a mind anyway?
It just causes more trouble.
Anyway, you've got to obey all of my orders. Do you hear?
Oh, this is stupid.
All personnel go to first stage 1. Prepare for aerial assault.
An Angel? Another one?
We have visual confirmation on the Angel.
Maximum magnification.
Its orbit is just outside our defense envelope, and it's maintaining a constant distance from us.
So, does that mean it's looking for a nice, comfy place to land?
Or that it's going to destroy us from way up there?
We can't attack it from this distance.
Yeah, and unless it decides to come into our range, there's not much we can do offensively.
The Ava's weren't designed to combat an enemy that's still in orbit.
How's Ray?
Ray and Unit 0 are both ready and waiting.
Understood.
Roll out Unit 0. Equip it for long-range firing.
Awesome, be ready to back her up in Unit 2.
Back her up? You want me to back up Unit 0?
That's right. Take the rear guard position.
You can't be serious. Ava, Unit 2, launch now!
Oscar!
It's okay. Let her take the point if that's what she wants.
Are you sure, Major?
If she screws this up, she won't be allowed to pilot anymore.
You mean this is her last chance?
Start preparing her replacement just to be safe.
Right.
Excuse me, aren't we going to use Unit 1?
Unit 1 states in cryostasis.
Those are Commander Ikari's orders.
And after what's happened, we better accept that.
If I fail this time, they won't let me pilot anymore.
You can do it, Oscar. You must.
The target is still out of range.
Damn! Why are you so slow? Come and fight, Angel!
The enemy has a particle beam on them?
No! No thermal emissions attacking!
Admiral Reedian, Oscar's psychograph!
Mental contamination imminent!
It's attacking across her ego borderline!
The Angels understand our psychology that well?
It's not working! It's too far out of time!
Damn! Her rifle is out of ammunition!
What's that beam made of?
It's some kind of energy oscillation using invisible wavelength!
It's similar to an AT field!
How's Oscar?
The mental contamination is crossing our ego borderline!
No! Don't!
No! Don't! Don't! Don't!
I'm sorry!
It's not working!
It's too far out of time!
Damn!
The rifle is out of ammunition!
What's that beam made of?
It's some kind of energy oscillation using invisible wavelength!
It's similar to an AT field!
How's Oscar?
It's similar to an 18 field.
How's Asuka?
The mental contamination is crossing our ego borderline.
No!
Don't come into me!
Don't!
Get out of my mind!
Please, guys!
Taking my mind!
Asuka!
We've got to get Asuka out of there immediately.
Her mind is going to be permanently damaged.
Asuka, retreat!
No!
Don't order, Asuka!
I'm ordering you to retreat!
No!
Never!
I'd rather die than admit defeat now!
Asuka!
Accelerator synchronization initiated.
Voltage is increasing.
Approaching pressure zone.
Compulsory focus convergence activated.
Compensation for the Earth's rotation and gravity 0.03.
Pressure in the chamber is at maximum.
Release the final safety locks.
All personnel, prepare for firing!
There wasn't enough energy to penetrate its AT field!
It's too far for our weapons!
But we're at maximum power output!
We can't get any more power!
Unit 2 Pleasure Red is getting a return!
What's the status on the LCL line barriers?
Negative!
We can't even hope for a buffering effect!
Switch to life support only!
Don't let it feed back into her!
I'll try.
Somehow that ray is scanning into Asuka's mental wavelength.
Are the angels trying to analyze what's inside a human mind?
Why am I crying?
I swore that I wouldn't cry anymore.
What's wrong, Asuka?
This was a present from your new mother.
Don't you like it?
No!
No, but why not?
Because I'm not a child!
I grew up faster than other people!
I didn't need a stupid stuffed toy!
Please!
Please look at me!
I'm begging you, Mama!
Don't stop being my mother!
Asuka!
Mama!
Come to heaven with me!
No!
Please!
Please don't kill me!
No!
I'm not Mama's doll!
I'll think for myself and I'll live for myself!
No!
Don't make me remember that!
I wanted to forget those things!
Don't uncover them!
I don't want those terrible memories anymore!
Stop this, please!
Stop it now!
My mind's being eaten away!
Kashi!
It's unraveling my mind!
What will I do?
It's defiling my mind!
Unit 2 MC's detonation!
Life support system crashed!
Pause my entering danger zone!
Position constant!
The target hasn't moved yet!
The possibility of the target coming into Unit 0's range is 0.02 percent!
Could we airlift Unit 0 and try an airborne attack?
No, that wouldn't work!
If the Angel attacked, we'd be defensive!
Misato!
Let me go out of Unit 1!
Forget it!
This angel's ability to attack the pilot's mind is too dangerous!
Yes, we cannot allow Unit 1 to be touched by an angel!
is zero point zero two percent could we airlift unit zero and try an airborne attack no that
wouldn't work if the angel attacked we'd be defensive misano let me go out of unit one forget
it this angel's ability to attack the pilot's mind it's too dangerous yes we cannot allow unit
one to be touched by an angel but that can't happen as long as i'm not defeated there is no
guarantee of that if we don't do something oscar will die that is true ray go to dogma and get the
lance use the lance of loginus you can't do that akari there is no other way to destroy a target
that remains in orbit beyond the reach of our at fields proceed but i thought that if adam and
ava were to come into contact it would cause the third impact we can't take that chance commander
it's much too dangerous so that story was another lie but if contact with an angel didn't cause second
impact then what did if something like this won't cause third impact then what really caused second
impact
akari it's too early to use the lance the committee has already started to mass produce avas this is
our chance our chance but we cannot make time run backwards but we can spur its course forward with our
own hands the old men won't allow this akari therefore we must finish this before salee has time to act
after all it is not acceptable to lose unit two at this time but you just can't use the range of
launching us without getting salee's approval first you have to keep her trouble the need is the justification
there are no other factors to consider the need you've just been looking for a convenient excuse
haven't you pilot to eg dropping to 0.06 we're past the limits of the life support system unit zero is
passing through vent two she'll be coming in over the surface
so that's the limits of launching us unit zero is in position to throw target sighted error corrections
have been made starting countdown 10 seconds till zero nine eight seven six five four three two one zero
the target annihilated ava unit two has been released i need a status update on the lance
it reached escape velocity it's now moving into a lunar orbit sir so it's almost impossible to
recover now right there are no methods available for recovering an object of that much mass
so unit two psychograph is returning to normal return the body to the second cage returning body via
access path 67 what's oscar status we've confirmed that the pilot is alive we've put her in quarantine
because of the contamination
hey i'm glad you're okay oscar shut up who in the hell is okay how can it get any worse
that little bitch that little bitch ray rescued me don't you know that i'd rather have died
i hate her i hate you shinji i hate everything
i hate you知 myself but i hate to get any worse of it
on the weather
so
for what i've worked on
too
get up
heavier
how is that
so
We'll be right back.
In this core, Rey chooses to make the ultimate sacrifice.
It all happens in tears.